EDMARK TUAZON

Cavite, Philippines · 09707688781/09675109949

edmark.softdev@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/edmarktuazon/



I' am self-taught, freelance/part-time Frontend Web Developer based in Cavite, Philippines I specialized in Frontend Web Development. I'm focus on creating responsive, and user-friendly websites, I use the latest frontend technologies to bring my client visions to project. I'm dedicated to providing good quality solutions that meet the needs and goals of my clients, as a self-taught Frontend Web Developer, I honed my skills through continuous learning and exploring.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT

PROJECT BASED JR. FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, TEMHOLIX COMMMUNICATION DESIGN INC.

- Build responsive and user-friendly websites for individuals, groups, startups, and small businesses.
- Converting UI/UX Designs into responsive Web Pages using latest Frontend
 Technologies (HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript and PHP)
- Implementing clean codes, test, report, and debug operations in the User Interface.
- Identifying and fixing website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and UI responsive issues.
- Handling (FTP FileZilla Client) for uploading in every done project and for UI Testing
- Collaborate with fellow Web Developer using GitHub

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

FREELANCE/PART-TIME FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, FIVERR AND OUTSIDE FIVERR

- Converting UI/UX Designs into responsive Web Pages using latest Frontend
 Technologies (HTML5, CSS3/SASS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript and PHP)
- Edit existing website of my client and supporting client's needs after a project

 Academic assisting and developing school projects of my student clients such as Web Development and Web Designing

EDUCATION

TERTIARY

JUNE 2020 - JULY 2023

ASSOCIATE DEGREE 2YEARS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY MAJOR IN APPLIED **COMPUTER SCIENCE, IMUS COMPUTER COLLEGE, CAVITE**

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

JULY 2018 - APRIL 2020

SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY ENGINEERING AND MATHEMATICS (STEM STRAND), SAINT

JUDE PARISH SCHOOL CAVITE

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND QUALIFICATION

- Programming (Fundamental Java, C++ and VB)
 Source Control Management (Git, GitHub)
- Web (HTML5, CSS3/SASS, Tailwind CSS,
 Adobe Creative Suite (Adobe XD, Figma) Bootstrap 4/5, JavaScript, VueJS, Fundamental ¡Query, TypeScript and PHP)

INTERNSHIP

SEPTEMBER 25, 2021 – FEBRUARY 22, 2022

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, LINKHELPERS INTERNATIOANAL INC.

- Completed 300 hours of On-the-job training remotely
- Created mockup using Figma and converted into responsive Web Page using (HTML5, SASS, JavaScript and Formspree)
- Worked on alternative Database server backend API
- Worked on SEO list directories

• Conducted daily report about the progress of my task

CERTIFICATES

• Certificate of completion - On-the-job training

LinkHelpers International Inc.

S.Y 2022 - 2023

• 1st Runner up - Web Development Competition

Imus Computer College, Cavite

November 2022

• Certificate of Participation - Introduction to Electronic Commerce using Shopify

Imus Computer College, Cavite

November 2022

REFERENCES

References are available upon request